# Awad Bin-Jawed

awadbinjawed@gmail.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/awadbinjawed/ (720)299-2608 · Aurora, CO 80017

I am a ServiceNow Developer with experience in delivering solutions to business needs. I created portals, applications and files, employing JavaScript, including AngularJS. I built powerful t tools that execute database operations via forms, all with user experience in mind.

#### Skills

	Н	Т	١/	ш	21	hh	CSS
_		ш	ıv	ш.	aı	11.1	( 1 2 3 )

- JavaScript
- REST/SOAP Web Services
- Debug Client & Server-side Scripts
- CRM
- Databases (SQL / Access)
- Health Information Systems
- Incident Management
- Research

## **Professional Experience**

SERVICENOW DEVELOPER - REVATURE Reston, VA

Mar 2019 - Jan 2020

- Leveraged ServiceNow's APIs and Editors to create responsive pages and incorporate widgets.
- Created **Catalog Items** and fine-tuned via workflow run scripts and catalog tasks.
- Configured Workflows according to client requirements.
- Crafted Notifications that execute from Business Rules and record insertions.
- Leveraged the JavaScript Log for Client Scripts and UI Policy Scripts (also UI Policy Debug).
- Leveraged the JavaScript Debugger for Business Rules.
- Leveraged the Script Editor to catch any runtime errors.
- Implemented Script Includes (extend GlideAjax) and new class to modularize lengthy (30 line) scripts.
- Tested Applications against User Access via **Debug Security Rules** (enable as admin, impersonate user).
- Tested Applications cross-scope access against other Applications via Runtime Access Tracking.

### Other Experiences

TIER 1 TECHNICAL SUPPORT – ASCENDA USA INC Aurora, CO
FULFILLMENT ASSOCIATE - AMAZON Denver, CO
PRODUCT SUPPORT ANALYST – ORTHOFI (Robert Half) Denver, CO
ADS SALES COORDINATOR – COMCAST Englewood, CO
DATA ANALYST – DISH NETWORK(ROBERT HALF) Englewood, CO
CLIENT ENGAGEMENT SPECIALIST - ZILLOW Centennial, CO
RESOLUTION TECHNICIAN – PATHOLOGY ASSOC MEDICAL LABORATORY - Lakewood, CO

Jan 2020 - May 2020 May 2018 - Mar 2019 Mar 2018 - May 2018 Oct 2017 - Feb 2018 Mar 2017 - Jun 2017 Mar 2016 - Mar 2017 Sep 2012 - Mar 2016

### Education

University of Colorado Denver - Public Health, B.A	Dec 2014
Galvanize - Python Programming, Denver Platte Center	Oct 2016
Coursera - R Programming, Certificate # KHRFQHFBMJ2E	Jan 2017
Udacity - Data Analyst, Nanodegree - License # 7P94NHZE	July 2018
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator, Certificate # 20131099	May 2019